# JESSAMYN MCTWIGAN

### AUSTIN, TX SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

I'm a creative, solutions-driven software developer with a passion for beautiful design, intuitive function and innate curiosity.

My past experience, overseeing the direction of venues and restaurants, has made me able to adapt quickly to find efficient solutions for any challenge.

#### CONTACT

904 347 1052
JESSAMYN-MCTWIGAN.SURGE.SH
JESSAMYN.MCTWIGAN@GMAIL.COM
LINKEDIN PROFILE
GITHUB PROFILE

### SKILLS

- PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES:
   Javascript, Python, JQuery,
   HTML5, CSS, Bash
- FRAMEWORKS | ENVIRONMENTS : Django, React.js, Node.js, EJS, Express.js, Mongoose
- DATABASES:
   MongoDB, Firebase, PostgreSQL

#### WEB DEVELOPMENT EXPERIENCE

### GENERAL ASSEMBLY WEB DEVELOPMENT IMMERSIVE AUSTIN, TX

JUN 2018 - SEP 2018

- Participated in a full-time Immersive Web Development course, completing a full stack training focused on current applications of real-world web development principles and best practices.
- Developed a portfolio of personal and collaborative projects including:
- Outdoor Austin | Full Stack App utilizing React, Django, Python, PostgreSQL, CSS
- Party Potensh | Full Stack App utilizing React, Express, MongoDB, EJS, Node.js, Bootstrap, Spotify API
- Cat v Baby Game | Full Stack App utilizing Express, Javascript, Node, MongoDB, Mongoose, CSS

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### MANAGER & EVENTS DIRECTOR AUSTIN, TX

BREW & BREW | NOV 2014 - JUN 2018

- Pursued, contracted, and directed events for Pitchfork, Samsung, Tinder, Car2Go, and over 100 other businesses
- Managed budgets and budget proposals for both the restaurant and event space
- Tracked timelines, budgets, and invoices using Google Suite

## GENERAL MANAGER ST AUGUSTINE, FL

CAFE ELEVEN | JUN 2006 - JUL 2013

- Pursued, contracted, and directed performances for The Flaming Lips, Modest Mouse, The Decemberists, Vampire Weekend and over 100 other bands
- Staffed, scheduled, budgeted, and oversaw general operations for the restaurant and venue

### EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION FLAGLER COLLEGE

STUDY OF FINE ARTS
MONTSERRAT COLLEGE OF ART